import React from "react";

const infoPair = [
    {
        question: "On which continent have the most dinosaur fossils been found?",
        answer: "North America",
    },
    {
        question: "When did dinosaurs become extinct?",
        answer: "65 million years ago",
    },
    {
        question: "When did dinosaurs first appear?",
        answer: "Triassic period",
    },
    {
        question: "For how many years did dinosaurs rule the earth?",
        answer: "165 million years",
    },
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur had a giraffe-like neck?",
        answer: "Brachiosaurus",
    },
    {
        question: "True or false? Birds evolved from dinosaurs.",
        answer: "True",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first carnivorous dinosaur to be discovered in Antarctica?",
        answer: "Cryolophosaurus",
    },
    {
        question: "How many teeth did Triceratops have?",
        answer: "800 teeth",
    },
    {
        question: "How did Stegosaurus protect itself from enemies?",
        answer: "Swinging its spiky tail",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first dinosaur to be discovered?",
        answer: "Megalosaurus",
    },
]

export default infoPair;